export const dragCode = {
    "21front": "u", "20front": "u", "10front": "u",
    "21right": "u", "20right": "u", "10right": "u",
    "21left": "u", "20left": "u", "10left": "u",
    "67back": "u", "68back": "u", "78back": "u",
    "12front": "U", "02front": "U", "01front": "U",
    "12right": "U", "02right": "U", "01right": "U",
    "12left": "U", "02left": "U", "01left": "U",
    "76back": "U", "86back": "U", "87back": "U",

    "67front": "d", "78front": "d", "68front": "d",
    "67right": "d", "78right": "d", "68right": "d",
    "67left": "d", "78left": "d", "68left": "d",
    "21back": "d", "20back": "d", "10back": "d",
    "76front": "D", "87front": "D", "86front": "D",
    "76right": "D", "87right": "D", "86right": "D",
    "76left": "D", "87left": "D", "86left": "D",
    "12back": "D", "02back": "D", "01back": "D",

    "25front": "R", "28front": "R", "58front": "R",
    "25top": "R", "28top": "R", "58top": "R",
    "25bottom": "R", "28bottom": "R", "58bottom": "R",
    "25back": "R", "28back": "R", "58back": "R",
    "52front": "r", "82front": "r", "85front": "r",
    "52top": "r", "82top": "r", "85top": "r",
    "52bottom": "r", "82bottom": "r", "85bottom": "r",
    "52back": "r", "82back": "r", "85back": "r",

    "03front": "l", "06front": "l", "36front": "l",
    "03top": "l", "06top": "l", "36top": "l",
    "03bottom": "l", "06bottom": "l", "36bottom": "l",
    "03back": "l", "06back": "l", "36back": "l",
    "30front": "L", "60front": "L", "63front": "L",
    "30top": "L", "60top": "L", "63top": "L",
    "30bottom": "L", "60bottom": "L", "63bottom": "L",
    "30back": "L", "60back": "L", "63back": "L",

    "67top": "f", "68top": "f", "78top": "f",
    "03right": "f", "06right": "f", "36right": "f",
    "21bottom": "f", "20bottom": "f", "10bottom": "f",
    "85left": "f", "82left": "f", "52left": "f",
    "76top": "F", "86top": "F", "87top": "F",
    "30right": "F", "60right": "F", "63right": "F",
    "12bottom": "F", "02bottom": "F", "01bottom": "F",
    "58left": "F", "28left": "F", "25left": "F",

    "21top": "b", "20top": "b", "10top": "b",
    "85right": "b", "82right": "b", "52right": "b",
    "67bottom": "b", "68bottom": "b", "78bottom": "b",
    "03left": "b", "06left": "b", "36left": "b",
    "12top": "B", "02top": "B", "01top": "B",
    "58right": "B", "28right": "B", "25right": "B",
    "76bottom": "B", "86bottom": "B", "87bottom": "B",
    "30left": "B", "60left": "B", "63left": "B",

    "14front": "m", "17front": "m", "47front": "m",
    "14top": "m", "17top": "m", "47top": "m",
    "14bottom": "m", "17bottom": "m", "47bottom": "m",
    "14back": "m", "17back": "m", "47back": "m",
    "41front": "M", "71front": "M", "74front": "M",
    "41top": "M", "71top": "M", "74top": "M",
    "41bottom": "M", "71bottom": "M", "74bottom": "M",
    "41back": "M", "71back": "M", "74back": "M",
    
    "34front": "e", "35front": "e", "45front": "e",
    "34right": "e", "35right": "e", "45right": "e",
    "34left": "e", "35left": "e", "45left": "e",
    "43back": "e", "54back": "e", "53back": "e",
    "43front": "E", "53front": "E", "54front": "E",
    "43right": "E", "53right": "E", "54right": "E",
    "43left": "E", "53left": "E", "54left": "E",
    "34back": "E", "45back": "E", "35back": "E",

    "34top": "s", "45top": "s", "35top": "s",
    "14right": "s", "17right": "s", "47right": "s",
    "54bottom": "s", "53bottom": "s", "43bottom": "s",
    "74left": "s", "71left": "s", "41left": "s",
    "43top": "S", "54top": "S", "53top": "S",
    "41right": "S", "71right": "S", "74right": "S",
    "45bottom": "S", "35bottom": "S", "34bottom": "S",
    "47left": "S", "17left": "S", "14left": "S",
}